(Raj:)I'd rather get a prostate exam
(Raj:)from a leper who walks away
with nine fingers.
(Priya:)Oh, would you please stop
feeling sorry for yourself?
(Raj:)I have to feel sorry for myself.
I'm the only one who cares.
(Raj:)Just like I'm the only one
who'll have sex with me.
(Leonard:)Really? In front
of your sister?
(Priya:)We shared a room growing up.
This is not news to me.
(Raj:)Excuse me. I'm going to go
wander the streets alone.
Invisible, unwanted and unloved;
(Raj:)a pathetic shadow
in a city with no heart.
(Raj:)I forgot my windbreaker.
It's chilly.
(Amy:)I don't understand. Is this
a way to break in new shoes?
(Penny:)No. Once these puppies
touch the ground
(Penny:)they're mine,
and I'll have to wear them
(Penny:)walking up and down
Hollywood Boulevard
(Penny:)in order to pay them off.
(Penny:)Pretty, pretty, pretty.
Good news: the wildebeest
is in the curry.
(Penny:)The what?